Eljhon Khyle Balderama

Address Purok 5, Poblacion, Baroy Lanao Del

Norte, Philippines 9210

Phone +639362393651

E-mail eljhonbalderama@gmail.com

I'm currently studying Computer Science at Christ The King College de Maranding, Inc. My passion lies in coding and creating captivating UI/UX designs, where I aim to craft visually appealing and user-friendly digital experiences. When I'm not immersed in technology, I love cooking and experimenting with flavors in the kitchen. I also have an insatiable curiosity that drives me to explore new realms, whether through travel, new hobbies, or staying up-to-date with emerging trends. Expanding my horizons is something I always look forward to.

Skills

Computer Programming	
Problem Solving	
Web Development	
Flexible and Adaptable	
Multitasking Abilities	
Planning and Coordination	

Work History

2023-08 - 2024-01

Virtual Assistant

Omnichannel

As an efficient and detail-oriented Virtual Assistant, I excel in managing executive calendars, and handling email correspondence. Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite and project management tools, I am adaptable to virtual collaboration environments. My expertise lies in multitasking, prioritizing tasks, and ensuring smooth administrative operations.

2020-11 - 2021-02

Call Center Agent

Dynata

Takes calls from customers answering questions or addressing any concerns they may have. Provide product and service information to customers. In charge of answering customer calls, listening to their concerns and solving problems. Handling both inbound and outbound phone conversations with clients to make sure everyone quickly gets the help they need.

Education

2020-08 - Current	Tertiary - BS: Computer Science
	Christ The King College De Maranding Inc Maranding Lala, Lanao Del Norte
2016-06 - 2018-03	Senior High School
	Santo Niño Academy Baroy, Inc Poblacion, Baroy Lanao Del Norte
2012-06 - 2016-03	Secondary
	Santo Niño Academy Baroy Inc Poblacion, Baroy Lanao Del Norte
2006-06 - 2012-03	Primary
	Baroy Central Elementary School - Poblacion, Baroy Lanao Del Norte